H. Alexander Smith Papers, 1897-1966 (bulk 1920-1966 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 4: Senatorial Career, 1931-1958; 159.67 linear feet 376 boxes
  - Subseries 4E: Public Issues, 1944-1958; 59.21 linear feet 142 boxes
    - 1958, 52 boxes (1 partial)
      - Woo, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Wool Tariff, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Wor-Wy, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Widnall, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Wila-Wilk, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Will, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Willow Grove Naval Air Station ,1958, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Wilm-Wilz, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Wim-Win, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - World Calendar, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Wrightstown Post Office, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - X-Y, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Young Republicans, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Z, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Agriculture, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Agriculture, Price Supports, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Agriculture, Surpluses, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Air Carriers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Aircraft Repairs, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Air Force Spending, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Air Parts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Alaska Statement, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Alcohol, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - American History Day, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Anti-Dumping, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Anti-Military Competition Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Anti-Trust, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Appropriations, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Appropriations, Agriculture, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Appropriations, Defense and Medicare, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Appropriations, Health, Education and Welfare, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Area Redevelopment, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Armed Services, 1958; 7 folders
        - Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - National Sovereignty, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Basic Pay, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Judge Advocates, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Day Six Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Draftee Release, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Reserve Officers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Arms Race, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Atomic, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Automobiles, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Bakers Licenses, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Bank Reserves, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Bankers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Believe In America Week, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Billboards, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Bricker Resolution, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Bridge Heights, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Brussels Fair, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Budget, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Campaign Contributions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Cancer, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Capital Extension, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Cigarettes, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Civil Defense, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Civil Service, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Civil Service Pay, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Civil Service Pensions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Civil Rights, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Cloture, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Commodity Exchange, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Competitive Rate Making, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Community Facilities, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Congress, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Conservation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Constitution Day, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Corregidor, Bataan Memorial, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Courts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Customs Service, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Cystic Fibrosis, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Deeping the Delaware, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Depository Libraries, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Defense Department, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Dinosaur National Monument, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Disarmament, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Disarmament Subcommittee, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - District of Columbia, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Domestic Mineral Stabilization, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Duck Feeding Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Economy, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Elections, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Electoral College, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Equality of Opportunity, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Equal Rights, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Far East, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Fair Trade, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Federal Aviation Agency, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Federal Boating Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Federal Construction Contract Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Federal Highways, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Federal Housing, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Federal Industrial Mortgage, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Federal Judgeships, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Federal Housing Operations Fees, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Federal Pay Raise, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Federal Reorganization, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Federal Rules and Procedure, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Financial Institutions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Fluoridation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Flying Saucers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Foreign Policy, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Foreign Service, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Foreign Trade Board, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Freight Forwarding, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Gaither and Rockefeller Reports, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Government Competition, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Grant’s Tomb, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Guides, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Hawaii, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - History Month, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Hog Cholera Vaccine, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Holidays, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Home Loan Guaranty, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Hoover Commission, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Human Rights, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Humane Slaughter, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Humane Trapping ,1958, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Immigration, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Immigration Commission,1958, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Immigration, McCarran Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - India, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Indians, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Indiana Dunes, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Individual Retirement, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Insecticides, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - International Cooperation Administration, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Integration, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Interstate Commerce, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Institutional Development Association, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Jewish Folder, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Juvenile Delinquency, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Kruschev Visit, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Labor, 1958; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Agriculture Workers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Aid to Schools, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Aid to Federal Impacted Areas, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Aid to Public and Parochial Schools, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Arts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Audio and Visual Aids, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Blind, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Business and Technical Schools, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - David-Bacon Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
        - Discrimination, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
        - Education, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 22)
        - Fair Labor Standards, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 23)
        - Food and Drug, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 24)
        - Health and Schools, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 25)
        - Higher Education, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 26)
        - Hospital Construction, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 27)
        - Mentally Retarded, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 28)
        - Minimum Wage, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Minimum Wage, Puerto Rico, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - National Labor Relations Board, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - National Labor Relations Board, Printers Union, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Overtime, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Profit Sharing, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Racketeers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Right to Work, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Safety, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Scholarships, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Scientific Education, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - School Construction, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Secondary Boycotts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - State Jurisdiction, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Supervisors, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Unemployment, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Unions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Unloading Fees, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Vocational Rehabilitation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Welfare and Pension, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Welfare and Pension, Level of Benefits, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Latin America, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Life Insurance, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Loyalty and Security Program, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Meat Inspection, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Meat Packing, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Merchant Marine Academy, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Middle East, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Milk, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Mineral Stabilization, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Missiles and Satellites, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Music Copyright, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Mutual Security, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Mutual Security, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - McCarthy, Joseph, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - National Capital Center for Performing Arts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - National Council for Negro Women, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - National Defense and Civil Defense, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - National Grange Building, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - National Library of Medicine, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - National Lottery, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - National Music Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - National Parks, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Natural Gas, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - New Jersey, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - New Jersey, Rent Control, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization Study, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Norstad’s Testimony, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Nisewaner, Andrew, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Nuclear Attack, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Nuclear Tests, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Nuclear Transfer, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Oil Imports, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Okinawa, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Onion Futures, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Outer Space, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Parcel Post, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Passenger Vessels, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Passports, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Payments to Municipalities, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Petroleum Products, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Philadelphia Wage Tax, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Poland, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Political Contributions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Post Office Department, 1958; 10 folders
        - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Postage Due, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Equipment, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Pay, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Per Diem, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Rates, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Weight Limits, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Rural Carriers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Saturdays, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - Venue, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Poultry, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - President’s Pensions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Presidential Disarmament, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Printing Processes, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Prisoners of War, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Public Lands, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Railroad Retirement, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Railroad Industry, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Radio, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Railroad Equipment Agency, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Railroad Rates, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Railroads and Water Transportation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Railroads, Trucker Opposition, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Recession Program, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Red China Recognition, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Religion, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Research and Development, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Rickover, Admiral, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Rural Electrification, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Reciprocal Trade, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Russia, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Savings and Loan, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Science and Research Institutions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Securities Registration, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Ships, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Small Business, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Social Security, 1958; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Age Limits, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Case Bills, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Earnings, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Forand Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Health, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Increase, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Old and Disabled, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Physicians, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Police and Firemen, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Self-Employed, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Widows, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Sons of the American Revolution, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Space and Aeronautics Administration, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Star Spangled Banner, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - States’ Rights, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Summit Meeting, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Sunday Law, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Super Liners, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Surplus Property, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Supreme Court Limitations, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Supreme Court Rulings, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Tariffs, 1958; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Copper, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - Japanese Flatware, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
        - Japanese Imports, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
        - Mica, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 22)
        - Umbrellas, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 23)
        - Wool, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Taxes, 1958; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Amusements, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Banks, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Business Expense Deductions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Capital Gains, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Co-ops, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Corps, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Cuts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Depreciation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Education Deduction, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
        - Electric Products, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Exempt Organizations, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
        - Excise, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
        - Federal Credit Unions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
        - Income, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Insurance, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Municipal Bonds, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - Police and Firemen, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - Reduction Program, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
        - Reform, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
        - Repairs, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 22)
        - Retirement Income Credit, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 23)
        - Sadlak, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 24)
        - Scholarships, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 25)
        - Small Business, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 26)
        - State Powers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Teachers, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Technical Amendments, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Transportation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Withholding, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Textiles, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Trade, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Trade With the Enemy, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Troops to the Middle East, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Tuna Fish, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - United Nations, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Un-American Activities, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Unemployment, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Urban Renewal, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Veterans, 1958; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
        - Beds, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
        - Disabled, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
        - G. I. Insurance, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
        - Home Loan, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Jewish Shrine, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - Korea, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Non-Service Disabled, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Preference, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - Refunds, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Service Committee, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Senate Security, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Spanish-American Widows, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - World War I, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Vivisection, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Wilderness Preservation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - War Department Beneficiary Association, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Wild Horses, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Water and Land Resources, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Wiretapping, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - World War II Damage Claims, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Agriculture Hall of Fame, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Aid to Airports Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Civil Aeronautics Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Air Carriers, Capital Gains, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Air Force Authorization Construction Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Agricultural Trade Development and Assistance Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Second Supplemental Appropriation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Appropriations, Treasury, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Antitrust and Monopoly Subcommittee, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Antitrust Laws, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Appropriations, Independent Offices, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, Proposal, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Appropriation Bill, Public Works, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Aviation Agency, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Budget, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Budget and Accounting Committee, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Budget, Joint Committee, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Byrd Report, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Community Facilities Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - National Cultural Center Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Eighty-fourth Congress, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Eighty-fifth Congress, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Committees, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Construction Programs, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Corn Acreage Allotment, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Cranberries, Agricultural Marketing Agreement Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Cultural Center, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Civil Rights, Clippings, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Civil Rights, Public School Segregation ,1958, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Civil Liberties, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Commission of Civil Rights, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Civil Rights, General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - President’s Committee on Government Contracts, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Economic Situation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Extension, East Front of Capital, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Farm and Agricultural Products, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Farm, Agricultural Bill, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Farm Legislation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Federal Construction Contract Procedures Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Federal-State Action Committee, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Supreme Court Decisions, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Gifts, Prohibition of, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - National Grammar Commission ,1958, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Highway Folder, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Home Rule, District of Columbia, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Housing, General, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Housing Legislation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Humane Slaughter, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Executive Information, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Inflation and Fiscal Policy, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Interpleader Contract, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Revision of Depository Library Laws, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Meat Packing, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Military Pay Bills, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - National Guard, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Natural Gas Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Natural Gas, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Neuberger, Senate Seniority, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Nixon, Richard, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Postal, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Pay Bills, Postal and Classified, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Polycultural Institution of America, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - President Eisenhower, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Presidential Disability, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Proposals to Relieve President of Certain Duties, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Railroads, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Transportation Act, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Railroad Truckers Situation, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Rivers and Harbors, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Rockefeller Report on United States Economy, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Senate Chamber Audio System, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Senate, Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Senate Rules, Cloture, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - A, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - B, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - C, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - D, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - E, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - F, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - G, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - H, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - I, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - J, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - K, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - L, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Mc, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - M, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - N, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - O, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - P, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - R, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - S, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 19)